Mathis Biabiany

Creative Technologist

Phone: +336 07 12 84 79

Mail: mathis.biabiany@gmail.com

Portfolio: http://www.mathis-biabiany.fr

I'm a creative technologist currently fighting the Amsterdam's winters at Resn. I'm passionate about the realisation of interactive digital effects providing cool sensations to the user. I like to work on installations, physical projects or websites with a nice experience.

Experience:

 Creative Developer at <u>Resn</u> (Amsterdam, Netherlands)

October 2016 - now

• Web Developer at **Touaregs** (Paris, France)

October 2013 – June 2016

• Web Developer at La Vie du Rail (Paris, France)

Avril 2013 - July 2013

Technical Skills:

- HTML5/CSS3/Javascript
- WebGL / GLSL

Education:

• CRMA, in Interactive and Digital media communication programmes.

Gobelins, l'école de l'image, Paris, France. 2014 – 2016

Bachelor Web Development and Mobile.

Gennevilliers, France.

2013 - 2014

• DUT SRC, Network & Services of Communication.

Sarcelles, France.

2011 - 2013

• BAC, in Sciences and Technologies of the Industry.

Saint-Denis, France.

2011

Awards:

- 2018: Célia Lopez FWA SOTD
- 2018: Célia Lopez AWWWARDS SOTD
- 2018: Célia Lopez **CSSDesignAwards SOTD**
- 2017: Resn Little Helper **AWWWARDS SOTD**
- 2017: Resn Little Helper **FWA SOTM**
- 2017: Christmas Experiment FWA SOTD
- 2017: DEVX Experiments AWWWARDS SOTD
- 2017: DEVX Experiments **FWA SOTD**
- 2017: DEVX Experiments CSSDesignAwards SOTD
- 2017: Adidas Speedfactory **AWWWARDS SOTD**
- 2017: Adidas Speedfactory FWA SOTD
- 2017: Adidas Speedfactory CSSDesignAwards SOTM
- 2017: Adidas NMD AWWWARDS SOTD
- 2017: Adidas NMD FWA SOTD
- 2017: Adidas NMD CSSDesignAwards SOTD
- 2016: Christmas Experiment FWA SOTD
- 2016: HP Sound in Color AWWWARDS SOTD
- 2016: HP Sound in Color FWA SOTD
- 2016: HP Sound in Color CSSDesignAwards SOTD
- 2015: Gobelins interactive experiments AWWWARDS SOTD
- 2015: Gobelins interactive experiments **FWA SOTD**